### Main menu

===============================================================

Menu Close

Search in International Brotherhood of Teamsters  

Privacy Policy
==============

**The International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT) is committed to protecting your privacy. This page explains how the IBT’s Strategic Initiative staff gathers and handles information from visitors to the Web site and reflects our dedication to securing the information you entrust with us.**

###### Personal Information

The only personal information Teamster.org collects is what you voluntarily provide through online registration forms, purchases or e-mails. This information may include your name, e-mail address, street address, phone number, membership status and local union affiliation. We do not store sensitive personal information.

Although, we do use the last four digits of your Social Security number to validate union membership, that information is not stored on our web servers. The information is checked against our secured membership database and deleted after authorization is granted.

The information you provide is used only to communicate with you (if you grant permission to do so) more effectively. Other information you submit through online forms is kept confidential. It will not be sold or shared with unaffiliated third parties, such as mass marketers.

Teamster.org provides personal information on a secure and confidential basis to third parties that have contracted with the IBT to offer services that it cannot offer on its own, such as selling merchandise, offering travel services or sending e-mail alerts.

These third-party providers are required to protect the privacy of IBT members and site visitors. They must safeguard your information and can use it only to complete the purchases or tasks you’ve authorized.

In accordance with the Children’s Online Protection Privacy Act (COPPA), Teamster.org does not knowingly collect, use or distribute personal information on children to any third party.

###### Secure Transactions

Agreements with third-party vendors require they use secure servers and Secure Socket Layer (SSL) encryption to protect the transmission and processing of payments and financial information. These agreements state that the vendors may store your information in order to make future purchases easier. Review the privacy policies of each Teamster partner for more details. IBT also has security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information collected from visitors to the web site.

###### Visitor Tracking

Teamster.org also collects nonindentifying information to help the IBT monitor and analyze usage patterns and web traffic, including the name of your Internet service provider, the browser you are using, the web site that referred you, the pages you visited while on the site and the date and time of your visits. We use this information on an aggregate basis to generate statistics that help us improve the usefulness of the site.

###### Use of ‘Cookies’

Cookies are very small files downloaded to your computer that contain information about the user. Cookies can be “persistent,” downloading to your hard drive and saved indefinitely, or “session,” downloading to a temporary folder and erased when you close your browser. Teamster.org uses only session cookies to help facilitate a few tasks on the site. The site does not use cookies to track other online activity. Likewise, Teamster.org does not partner with or have special relationships with any ad server companies.

###### Opting Out of E-mails

Teamster.org will only send email that you have signed up to receive. If you wish to stop getting email from us, choose the “opt out” link in the message or write to [strategicinitiatives@teamster.org](mailto:strategicinitiatives@teamster.org). Teamster.org does not send unsolicited email nor does it send emails requesting personal or financial information. Delete emails you believe to be suspicious.

###### Off-site Links

Teamster.org contains links to other sites. The IBT is not responsible for the privacy practices or content of other web sites. Be aware when you leave our site and review privacy statements before divulging your personal information. This privacy policy applies solely to Teamster.org.

###### Policy Changes

Technology is always advancing. So the IBT reserves the right to change this privacy policy, to change the information we collect from visitors to our webpage, and to change the way in which we use that information.

###### Contact Information:

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| **Email:** | [strategicinitiatives@teamster.org](mailto:strategicinitiatives@teamster.org) |
| **Mail:** | Teamster.org  <br>  <br>c/o Strategic Initiatives Dept.  <br>International Brotherhood of Teamsters  <br>25 Louisiana Avenue  <br>  <br>Washington, DC 20001 |
| **Phone:** | 202-624-6911 |

=============================================================================

#### International Brotherhood of Teamsters

25 Louisiana Avenue, N.W.

Washington D.C., 20001

Facebook Twitter Instagram YouTube TikTok Close Menu Car Person Credit Card College Email Arrow Left Arrow Right Quote
